

Toni Dzhambazov

PORTFOLIO:

tonidzhambazov.ml

DATE OF BIRTH:

12/1994

CONTACT



tonidzhambazov@gmail.com



(+359) 886768001

LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/</u> tonidzhambazov

ABOUT MF

Upon graduating from the American University in Bulgaria in 2017, I set myself on the personal mission to be exceptional. By my last year there, I had enough people interested in my skills to start a 3-year journey in the world of freelance.

Working with individuals and businesses globally, handling small and medium projects, and leading a tight team involved with six-figure corporations, I was able to learn even more and further hone in my skills and discipline.

Now, I'm looking for a team that will push me to get even better. All that I have learned, all that I can contribute and all that I will continue to learn goes to the company that inspires me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2017 - CURRENT - Sofia, Bulgaria

Web developer

Freelance

Creating web solutions & websites, solo & as leader of a small team

Responsibilities include:

- maintain proper channels of communications between my team and our clients.
- troubleshoot critical situations with short timelines,
- and of course, write fullstack code

Experience working globally with small, medium and six-figure companies in the following sectors:

- Technology, media and telecommunications
- Manufacturing
- Financial and insurance activities
- Arts, entertainment and recreation
- Accommodation and food service activities

05/2017 - CURRENT - Sofia, Bulgaria

Graphic designer

Freelance

Deliver graphic design services while focusing on:

- creating a strategy that best fits the client's vision,
- design creation & integration of web & print graphics,
- ensuring that my clients remain inspired long after my part is done

06/2017 - 06/2018 - Bulgaria

Business consulting

Freelance

Took charge of a team of 5 entrepreneurs to consult local small and medium businesses to improve management of internal operations, marketing strategies and leadership techniques.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

05/2017 - Bulgaria

Bachelor's degree in Business administration

American University in Bulgaria

Led a team of young entrepreneurs in winning third place in the AUBG StartUp Challenge 2016 with an original idea to popularize Bulgarian arts&crafts culture abroad through a web platform solution.

Field of study

Leadership & Marketing

Cum laude | EQF level 6 | www.aubq.edu

05/2017 - Bulgaria

Bachelor's degree with honors in Information Systems

American University in Bulgaria

Defended a Senior Project with a mark of excellence - design and deployment of an online open-source platform, which supports campaign development and storytelling for WotC's Dungeons&Dragons.

Field of study

Design & development

Cum laude | EQF level 6 | www.aubq.edu

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE: Bulgarian

English

Listening Reading Spoken Spoken Writing
C2 C2 production interaction C2
C2 C2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Development technologies

HTML5 / Javascript / jQuery / CSS3 / Bootstrap / React / Angular / Vue.js / PHP / Wordpress / C# / MySQL / ASP.NET MVC

Design tools

Adobe Photoshop CC / Adobe Creative Suite / Adobe InDesign / Adobe Illustrator CC / Adobe Animate / CorelDRAW / Microsoft Office Suite

Interpersonal skills

Leadership / Visual Communication / Inter-cultural Communication / Self-Management / Team Lead & Team Player